hytale.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy – Hytale

We here at Hypixel Studios Inc. (“Hypixel”) know the importance of your privacy and value it as much as you do. To that extent, we use as little of your information as possible but wish to fully inform you of what information we do collect when you visit our website. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) will explain what information we collect online and why we collect it. This Policy describes the data practices of Hypixel covering its services under its control, including this website (collectively "Services"). By using the Services, you are consenting to this Policy and the processing of your data in the manner provided in this Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use the Services.

## Information Hypixel Collects

Hypixel may collect information about the Services you use and how you use them, such as the selections you make on our Services. We may collect PII and DII (as defined below) when you use the Services.

Personally identifiable information (“PII”) is information that can be used to identify or contact you online or offline, such as your name, address, email, phone number, photos or audio data, and payment information. The Services may collect PII only when it is provided to Hypixel and at no other time. Specifically, if you submit an email with your name and email address or if you fill out a contact form, Hypixel collects such information. At the present time, and in no other way, other than the ways just described, does Hypixel collect your PII.

Hypixel may also create or collect device-identifiable information (“DII”), such as cookies, unique device identifiers, and similar identifiers that are linkable to a browser or device. From these platforms, we may also receive other information, such as your IP address, user agent, timestamps, precise and imprecise geolocation, sensor data, apps, fonts, battery life information, and screen size. Specifically, Hypixel utilizes Google Analytics. To read about how Google uses your DII when you use the Services please review this link: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

## How Hypixel Uses the Information Collected

Hypixel uses the information we collect from our Services to provide, maintain, protect, and improve our Services, to develop new Services and offerings, and to protect us and our users.

PII is primarily used for business purposes, such as for sending you correspondence. When you contact Hypixel, Hypixel may keep a record of your communication as well as the other information associated with this correspondence in our database. The database is located on a server managed by Hypixel and no other party has access to this PII. Hypixel may use your email address to inform you about our Services, such as letting you know about changes or improvements and responding to your inquiries. Hypixel may share your PII with third-party services to send out correspondence such as MailChimp but does not share it with any other third-party.

Hypixel uses DII to operate Services and manage user sessions, including analyzing usage of our Services, preventing malicious behavioral and fraud, improving the content, to link your identity across devices and browsers in order to provide you with a more seamless experience online, and helping third parties provide relevant advertising and related metrics. We share DII with Google primarily for advertising and analytics purposes, for external processing, and for security purposes.

## Third Parties

While Hypixel strives to work with reputable companies with good privacy practices, this Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be used in association with the Services. For further information, please see the relevant privacy policies for each third party and industry codes of conduct.

## Choice

If you do not wish to share with Hypixel the above detailed information, please do not use the Services.

## Information Security

Hypixel works hard to protect our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold and undertake reasonable security measures with appropriate confidentiality, integrity, and availability protections. However, since no software or storage system is 100% secure, Hypixel cannot guarantee the security of your information associated with the Services, or any other service for that matter.

## Children Under 13

We do not knowingly collect information for any child under the age of 13. If you are the parent of a child under the age of 13 and have a concern regarding your child’s information on our Services, please contact us at the email provided at the end of this Policy.

## Storage of Your Information

Your information will be processed and stored in any other place where Google servers or Hypixel servers are located and you are consenting to such transfer, processing, and storage.

## Consent

By using the Services you consent to this Privacy Policy, the use of cookies, and any other information herein detailed.

## Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Policy changes on this page, including material changes. Please check back periodically to view changes to our privacy policy.

## Questions?

If you have questions or requests regarding your privacy, please contact us at privacy@hypixelstudios.com.

This Policy was last updated on **1 December, 2018**.
